<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Machine Learning Stuffs</title>
    <link>https://moisesvw.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Machine Learning Stuffs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://moisesvw.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PNASNet-5 Transfer Learning to Predict Animal Attributes</title>
      <link>https://moisesvw.github.io/projects/pnasnet-5-transfer-learning-to-predict-animal-attributes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moisesvw.github.io/projects/pnasnet-5-transfer-learning-to-predict-animal-attributes/</guid>
      <description>This project aims to build a predictive model that learn to identify attributes associated with each animal. It was part of hackerearth.com Challenge. It provides 18.000 images of 50 different categories, 12.600 have animal characteristics. These characteristics are treated as labels to train a predictive model that learns to map animal images to attributes. This set of 12600 images will be the training set.
Metrics There are 85 different attributes per image in the training set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Driving Cars (10) Projects </title>
      <link>https://moisesvw.github.io/projects/self-driving-cars-10-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moisesvw.github.io/projects/self-driving-cars-10-projects/</guid>
      <description>About Here there are all of the projects I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on during the Udacity&amp;rsquo;s Self Driving Car Engineer Nanodegree program.
Term 1 Finding Lane Lines I have detected highway lane lines on a video stream — used OpenCV image analysis techniques to identify lane lines, including Hough Transforms and Canny edge detection.
Traffic Sign Classifier Built and trained a deep neural network to classify traffic signs, using TensorFlow. Experimented with different network architectures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Engineer Nanodegree (7) Projects </title>
      <link>https://moisesvw.github.io/projects/machine-learning-engineer-nanodegree-7-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moisesvw.github.io/projects/machine-learning-engineer-nanodegree-7-projects/</guid>
      <description>Machine Learning Engineer Nanodegree About This repository contains projects associated with Udacity&amp;rsquo;s Machine Learning Engineer Nanodegree, that I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on. All the code can be find here https://github.com/moisesvw/udacity-machine-learning
Projects 1 - Predicting Boston Housing Pricing Built a model to predict the value of a given house in the Boston real estate market using various statistical analysis tools. Identified the best price that a client can sell their home utilizing machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
